Gerard P. Kuiper papers 1894-1992 (bulk 1949-1973)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series XVII: Slides, 1948–1974.
  - Subseries 2: The slides in this subseries are organized into yellow slide boxes. Slide boxes (folders) 1 through 263 are dated from 1952 to 1974. Slide boxes numbered 263 to 372 are undated. The majority of boxes do have labels. I have done my best to transcribe the labels., April 1965 – May 197
    - Flight Fernandez and Moran, San Manuel collapse depression; Catalina Observatory,; January 2, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 105)
    - End of Fernandez and Moran trip (Tumamoc), apartment on 2nd street; trips to Catalina with Mel and Hunt,; January 1967 (Box 70, Folder 106)
    - Trip east, January 24, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 107)
    - Acceptance of dormitory Site I, trip to Grants lava flow I; January 23, 1967; January 30-31, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 108)
    - Dr. Dobar, trip to Grants lava flow II; moving 16” to Tumamoc Hill,; January 30-31, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 109)
    - W. Hoek visit, January 31-Feb 14, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 110)
    - Garden, Polarscope; February 1967 (Box 70, Folder 111)
    - Trip to Los Angeles, visit of Capt. Mercer; trip to Washington; February 8, 1967; February 23, 1967,; February 14-15, 1967, (Box 70, Folder 112)
    - Home flowers and Lucy, March 26 –April 5, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 113)
    - Lucy leaving, San Xavier Mission and Lucy; April 9, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 114)
    - At Catalina, to San Francisco; April 6-7, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 115)
    - NASA 990 Jet, April 21-23, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 116)
    - NASA 990 Jet, April 24, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 117)
    - Visit to see Paul after Surveyor III JPL session, April 29, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 118)
    - Trip to Dallas, May 13, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 119)
    - Sunset, May 15,1967; May 21,1967 (Box 71, Folder 120)
    - Dormitory, Paul; garden,; May 15,1967; May 21,1967 (Box 71, Folder 121)
    - Flight 116, June 13, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 122)
    - [missing] (Box 71, Folder 123)
    - Trip to Ames, July 13-14, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 124)
    - Flagstaff trip, ACIC staff; Oak Creek Canyon,; July 1967 (Box 71, Folder 125)
    - Rain and sun, August 1967 (Box 71, Folder 126)
    - Trip to Europe IAU, August 19-26, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 127)
    - Excursion to Carlsbad IAU, August 26, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 128)
    - Excursion to Carlsbad IAU, August 27, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 129)
    - IAU, August 29, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 130)
    - Trip to Europe (Konopiste, Eindhoven, Frankfurt), August 29-September 4, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 131)
    - Visit to Site I Catalina Observatory, trip to JPL (Surveyor 5); September 8-12, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 132)
    - Catalina Observatory, September 17, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 133)
    - Catalina Observatory site I, September 30 – October 4, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 134)
    - Baha Island moon and sky colors, October 9-10, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 135)
    - Trip to Salt Lake, Utah, October 11, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 136)
    - Salt Lake, San Andreas fault; Sierra, Nevada; October 11, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 137)
    - San Andreas fault, Lick Observatory; October 11, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 138)
    - Lick Observatory, High Altitude telescope in CV990; October 11--12, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 139)
    - Circling over Catalina Island, Mt. Wilson; October 12, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 140)
    - Catalina Island and LA smog, San Andréa’s Fault; Mt. Wilson;; interior shots of Solar Spectra,; October 12, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 141)
    - Visit to site II (Air Force 5 ft. telescope), Flight to San Francisco via Monterey and Carmel; October 15-16, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 142)
    - Trip to Hawaii, October 19-22, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 143)
    - Trip to Hawaii, October 22, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 144)
    - Trip to Hawaii, October 23, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 145)
    - Hawaii Departure, San Francisco arrival; Catalina trip; October 24-November 16, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 145+)
    - Engineering Flight 990 Jet, landing sunrise; San Francisco with Paul;; his cottage; October 24-November 16, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 146)
    - Paul and his cottage, Sonoma College and Paul’s exhibit; November 19, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 147)
    - Redwoods on Russian River, California, November 19, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 148)
    - Dr. Swings visit, Grand Canyon; Lake Mead;; Las Vegas;; Sierra Nevada,; November 19-25, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 149)
    - Venus flight, Santa Cruz; University of California,; November 27-28, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 150)
    - Snow, Lucy home; Sabina Canyon,; December 17, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 151)
    - Lucy, Paul; Christmas dinner,; December 24-25,1967 (Box 72, Folder 151a)
    - Family (Paul and Lucy), December 29-31, 1967; January 1-3, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 152)
    - [missing] (Box 72, Folder 153)
    - Last views of Kilo, Hawaii, Dr. Oort’s visit; January 1-3, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 154)
    - Flowering Almond and Orange trees, Trip to Catalina; Snow on Catalina’s;; Waterfalls Sabino,; March 1968 (Box 72, Folder 155)
    - Lucy home, Pierre Connes visit; T. Cunningham and Herbert Frey,; March 26-30, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 156)
    - Jean Marc visit, Denver; Pasqua; April 1-19, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 157)
    - Southwest Research Station, Chiricahuas; April 12-13, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 158)
    - Visit of Fenny Kuiper, April 12-13, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 159)
    - Flight to Ames, trip to Santa Cruz; June 30, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 160)
    - Return flight from San Francisco to Tucson, Cloud pattern over Pacific; San Andreas Fault;; forest fire north of LA; July 3, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 161)
    - Flight to Ames, California smog; San Francisco Peaks,; smog Avra Valley,; July 10, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 162)
    - Flight Tucson to San Francisco, Tumamoc Observatory; smog at 14000 feet west of Tucson;; Sierra Nevada and smog;; San Francisco approach,; July 14, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 162+)
    - Return flight from San Francisco to Tucson, Bay Shore to nowhere; Sierra Nevada;; demolition on 3rd Street;; Sarah,; July 11-12, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 163)
    - First flight NASA 990 Solar Spectra, out east and back west of Shasta Bay area; off again to Lake Wells, Nevada,; July 11-12, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 164)
    - Return flight; Sierra Nevada (Mono Lake), San Joaquin Valley; burning off fuel over Monterey Bay;; Stanford,; July 16, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 165)
    - Salt Lake, Wind River Range; Mt. Rainier;; Three Sisters-Oregon;; Carter Lake;; Shasta;; Lick Observatory,; July 17-18, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 166)
    - Wind River Range (Wyoming), Shasta – Cloud Street; San Francisco Bay views,; July 19, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 167)
    - Trip to Catalina Observatory and cleanup of grounds, July 25, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 168)
    - Catalina Observatory Site I, Trip to LA and San Francisco; July 27-29, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 169)
    - Salt Lake City, Mt. Rainier; Crater Lake;; July 30, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 170)
    - Lick foothills, Half Moon Bay; NASA flight,; July 30-August 1, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 171)
    - NASA flight and return to Tucson, cloud cirrus thunderhead; August 2-4, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 172)
    - Return from Ames/LA smog, Walter Sidor visit; Appleton Ranch,; August 2-4, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 173)
    - Return flight to Tucson, August 6-7, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 174)
    - Return flight, Appleton Ranch (cloudscapes), August 7-11, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 175)
    - Moon, departure of pilot from Rancho San Jose; views from ranch;; test dome and surroundings;; new road being cut,; August 14, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 176)
    - Moon, departure of pilot from Rancho San Jose; views from ranch;; test dome and surroundings;; new road being cut,; August 14, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 177)
    - Flight from Tucson to Baja, pictures of Green Valley; Mt Hopkins;; Nogales;; clouds east of gulf;; Jorge Island;; Rocky Island;; San Felipe and bay shore,; August 14, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 177)
    - Flight from San Felipe to Rancho San Jose, August 14, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 178)
    - Base camp, Astronauts house under construction; blue sky before sunset;; view from dome;; California smog from dome;; early morning from base camp,; August 15-16, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 179)
    - Group coming to base camp to test site with families, April 15, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 180)
    - Toby Owens visit, Jean Marc visit; ; front and back views of home; September 1968 (Box 73, Folder 181)
    - Jean Marc visit to Tucson, September 1968 (Box 73, Folder 182)
    - Trip to Mt. Hopkins and Smithsonian Observatory, October 15, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 183)
    - Trip to Mt. Lemmon and to VA, October 20, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 184)
    - Monticello with John Wood, October 21, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 185)
    - Trip to Green Bank NRAO West Virginia and University of Virginia, October 22, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 186)
    - Kitt Peak National Observatory from distance, San Manuel Smelter smoke; Hayden;; Globe; sink holes in Winslow,; October 26,1968 (Box 73, Folder 187)
    - University of VA, Return to Tucson from West Virginia-Chicago; trip to Catalina Observatory with Mikchailou,; October 21-22, 26, 1968; October 26, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 188)
    - Meteor Crater; Sunset Crater; Grand Canyon, [October 26, 1968] (Box 73, Folder 189)
    - Grand Canyon, San Francisco Peaks; U.S. Naval Observatory;; Oak Creek Canyon;; smog n. Roosevelt Lake,; [October 26, 1968] (Box 73, Folder 190)
    - [missing] (Box 73, Folder 191)
    - Shots around the house, Paul’s opening at La Gracias; McDonald Observatory dedication,; November 24- 26, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 192)
    - McDonald Observatory 107”- return trip, Christmas vacation at home; November 27, 1968,; December 1968 (Box 74, Folder 193)
    - Venus flight off Baja California and return, Robert Murphy and Dale Cruikshank; Site II (road and snow),; January 22 – February 2, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 194)
    - Sunset at high altitude, Pentagon, rainbow on clouds; Lucy at home;; Soldier Peak Summit;; Tucson and Catalina’s’,; January 22 – February 2, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 195)
    - Venus flight, reflected sun on ice crystals Mt Hood and shore-line; February 1969 (Box 74, Folder 196)
    - Venus flight, Crater Lake; February 1969 (Box 74, Folder 197)
    - Lake Tahoe, Nevada in snow; Salt Lake;; San Francisco Bay;; Monterey Bay;; Sierra Nevada,; February 7, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 198)
    - Flight Mt. Hood (full snow cover), shore of Pacific (clouds); February 7, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 199)
    - Mt. Lemmon, San Francisco Peaks; Flagstaff;; Grant lava tunnels,; March 12, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 200)
    - Flight - Meteor Crater, Grants’ lava flow; March 12, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 201)
    - Flight – Grant flows and Mt. Taylor, Morenci Smoke; March 12, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 202)
    - Kuiper, Minnaert, and Kittel at Desert Museum, smog trip with NIH Panel; lava and fish at home,; March 17, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 203)
    - Lucy, Marc, Paul at home; March 20, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 204)
    - Solar home on Mt. Lemmon, flowering trees at home; trip to Colorado and Pikes Peak,; April 1969 (Box 74, Folder 205)
    - Pikes Peak, down to Colorado Springs, Garden of the Gods; April 12, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 206)
    - Views in garden, Washington D.C. International Airport; April 1969 (Box 74, Folder 207)
    - Inspection of Site II, Site I (ground moving); April 22, 1969; April 29, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 208)
    - Approaching Hawaiian Island, Honolulu, Pearl Harbor; trip to east shore Oahu,; May 1-4, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 209)
    - [missing] (Box 74, Folder 210)
    - Charter flight west and south coast of Maui Hawaii, waterfalls; Hilo Bay;; eruption SW of Haleakala North Ocean,; May 5, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 211)
    - Charter flight Kilauea Hei, Halemaumau Crater; chain of carters;; Mauna Kea;; Molokimi,; May 5, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 211+)
    - Flowers at home, trip to San Francisco; trip to Hawaii,; May 20-28, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 212)
    - Views from Reef Hotel, Waikiki, May 31, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 213)
    - Trip to Mauna Kea (Part I), June 1, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 214)
    - Visit to Mauna Kea views, Mauna Kea from Hilo; June 1– June 2, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 215)
    - Trip to Hilo Maui, Haleakala; Advanced Research Projects;; Agency (ARPA) Observatory;; Mauna Kea,; June 2, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 216)
    - Dedication of 90 inch at Kitt Peak, flight to Flagstaff; July 19, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 217)
    - CBS Flagstaff – Moon Landing, July 20,1969 (Box 75, Folder 218)
    - Man on the Moon with US flag, return from CBS Flagstaff; 2 shots from home,; July 1969 (Box 75, Folder 219)
    - Bok at Site I, Lucy at home in garden; Harold Larson visit;; San Manuel and Hayden;; panorama view from Mount Bigelow,; August 10-25, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 220)
    - To Houston, Surveyor; Cirrus clouds;; Page farewell,; August 26-29, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 221)
    - Home garden, Catalina Observatory clouds; September 10, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 222)
    - View from study window, Lucy, JM, Paul in Hawaiian shirt; JM place in Tubac Lucy, Sarah;; Lucy in Nogales;; trip to Houston;; Franklin Mountains;; McDonald Observatory,; September 14-17, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 223)
    - At home, JPL Mercury; Lucy and Sarah front yard,; September 1969 (Box 75, Folder 224)
    - Site IV Catalina Observatory, at home front and back yard; October 1969 (Box 75, Folder 225)
    - IAU 40th Conference Marfa, October 1969 (Box 75, Folder 226)
    - Smog from Windy Point toward Kitt Peak, construction of Site IV, 40”, dome; views from Mt. Lemmon;; smog from San Manuel Smelter;; Mt. Lemmon road,; November 11-16, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 227)
    - Family, November 20-December 1, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 228)
    - [missing] (Box 75, Folder 229)
    - Views of Catalina’s, front yard; [January 1970] (Box 75, Folder 230)
    - Panorama from Windy Point, panorama from Geology Vista; Harvard College Observatory;; Whipple’s office,; [January 1970] (Box 75, Folder 231)
    - Boston Logan airport, Boston vicinity smog, snow; Connecticut River;; Lake Ontario (Syracuse west);; Lake Huron ice fields;; Evaporation particles on Lake Michigan,; January 22, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 232)
    - Construction Mt. Lemmon 40" USRA, Weaver’s trip to Mt. Lemmon; February 2-3, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 233)
    - German TV at Catalina Observatory, Mt. Lemmon inspection; February 21-25, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 234)
    - Flight Mt. Lemmon, Tucson; Tumamoc;; Catalina Observatory;; Mt Graham;; Hiliago PR,; March 7, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 235)
    - Miller Peak, Mt Wrightson; Mt. Hopkins; March 7, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 236)
    - Paul's wedding, March 22, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 237)
    - Flight to San Diego via Palmas views; roses at home, April 12- 19, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 238)
    - Flowers at home, trip to Mt. Agassiz; May 6, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 239)
    - Mt. Agassiz, Mt Humphreys; May 6, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 239+)
    - Palomar 60”, 200”, return trip clouds over desert new Salton Sea; hard-hat demonstration;; to Colorado Springs,; June 1, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 240)
    - Colorado Springs and Pikes Peak, view of Pikes Peak from airport; Broadmoor suite;; views from Glen Cove,; June 2, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 241)
    - Return from Pikes Peak by road; ascent by cog rail road, June 2, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 242)
    - Pikes Peak ascent by cog rail road, June 3, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 243)
    - Mt. Lemon inspection with Houston, Off to Hawaii; California desert and smog;; Mt. Wilson;; Santa Barbara Island,; June 24, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 244)
    - Pacific clouds, Mauna Kea; Rainbow Honolulu;; Diamond Head;; Maui;; Kilo Bay;; Mauna Kea,; June 24, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 245)
    - Brunk and Newell on Kilauea Iki, Lava Tree Park; Kapoho;; Halemaumau Crater;; chain of craters road;; Hilo County building;; Mauna Kea,; June 26-28, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 246)
    - Flight to San Francisco, fog on ocean; ripples; flight to Shasta,; July 6-7, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 247)
    - Lucy and des Tombe, California, July 8, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 248)
    - Meeting on Mt. Lemmon, smelter smog Tucson/Flagstaff; Flagstaff airport moon;; storm over Sedona and north Phoenix,; clouds at sunset Soldier Peak,; July 15-18, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 249)
    - [missing] (Box 76, Folder 250 and 251)
    - Trip to Catalina Observatory with John Summer, construction of Schmidt Dome; J.M. des Tombe and Lucy sees me off;; clouds,; April 9, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 252)
    - Clouds over Atlantic, August 15-16, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 253)
    - Nick’s house Eindhoven, old building; Uncle Dick and other family;; Uncle Dick and Sarah at Schiphol,; August 17-21, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 254)
    - Albion Beach, ;Bignor Roman Villa; Victorian flats for British court,; August 22, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 255)
    - Salisbury Cathedral, Stonehenge; Isle of Wight;; Polish ship; relief map of Mars; August 23, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 256)
    - Schmidt dome under construction, Isle of Wight; Polish ship; relief map of Mars; August 23, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 257)
    - Mt. Hopkins dedication, September 29, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 258)
    - Owens Valley, sand dunes from Arizona; Schmidt dome and 61” dome,; September 1970 (Box 76, Folder 259)
    - Paul, September-October (Box 76, Folder 260)
    - Trip to Ames/NASA regarding Lear Jet Solar Spectra program, shots of Lick Observatory and Moffett Field; October 6, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 261)
    - Visit of Dr. Heller and staff, garden from home study; back garden;; Paul and Sarah fountain front yard;; Sarah in back yard,; October 9, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 262)
    - Catalina Mountains yellow flower brush, garden views; visit by Robert E.Vehlin;; aero jet;; visit to Kitt Peak,; October 25-28, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 263)
    - Pima College, old airport hangar; new Anklan Rd,; November 7, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 264)
    - Front yard, fall colors, Minnesota Dome foundation Mt Lemmon; Molina Canyon fall colors;; Douglas smelter smoke going NW; lava fields west of Las Cruces, NM;; El Paso smoke sources,; November 8-11, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 265)
    - Minnesota dome foundation Mt. Lemon, NASA Ames Lear Jet test; November 14-17, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 266)
    - Installation in Lear Jet, White Mountains from Nevada; Mono Lake;; Sierra Nevada;; San Joaquin Valley;; Santa Cruz,; November 17, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 267)
    - Douglas smog from Windy Point, Minnesota dome going up; Air Force Lunar Laser;; home/garden;; Paul and Diana Thanksgiving,; November 1970 (Box 77, Folder 268)
    - Oakland to Bishop, December 5, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 269)
    - Bishop to Barcroft by helicopter, December 5, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 270)
    - To Bishop by helicopter, sunset on Sierra Nevada; December 5, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 271)
    - University of Minnesota dome and telescope, December 11-12, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 272)
    - Balloon experiments on 70” platform, at home front and back yard; January 15, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 273)
    - Panorama Mt Lemmon, at home; views of sky and sun at Soldiers Peak;; Apollo 14 launch on TV,; January 30-31, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 274)
    - [missing] (Box 77, Folder 275)
    - Fire on 22nd Street, Tucson, pine garden; earth's shadow /to Goddard;; Washington D.C. to Phoenix, meanders in rivers, Ohio River;; cross parallel clouds; March 1971 (Box 77, Folder 276)
    - Home front gardens, Views from roof of Space Science building; clean up on Mt Lemmon;; Air force dome structure;; views of flowers from home;; Mo Udall visit to Mt. Lemmon;; L. Maggio and Sarah on Mt Lemmon; April 7-10, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 277)
    - Front yard, Sarah, flowers (roses) in back of home; Lucy's garden, just completed;; Mt. Lemmon visit, Air Force dome,; April 11-17, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 278)
    - Home, Mt. Lemon demolition of annex building; test flight NASA CV990 (5000 lbs fuel dump),; April-May 1971 (Box 77, Folder 279)
    - Return from San Francisco, garden at home (roses pool, rocks); Mt. Lemon Air Force dome, demolishing part of safe annex,; May 7-14, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 280)
    - Yard at home, roses, rocks, palms, views from windows, telescope arrives from White Sands, New Mexico; Mt Lemon AFCRL telescope and dome,; June 1971 (Box 77, Folder 281)
    - [missing] (Box 77, Folder 282)
    - Tumamoc Hill testing and road work, August 1971 (Box 77, Folder 283)
    - Home to Baja via Hermosillo, August 29, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 284)
    - Survey n. San Jose del Cabo, August 29, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 285)
    - San Lucas to La Paz, August 30, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 286)
    - La Paz to Isla Espíritu Santo, August 30, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 287)
    - From Mulege to Tortuga Island to Calmalli, August 31, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 288)
    - September 12, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 289)
    - Lucy departs for JAVA, September 14, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 290)
    - Back yard, porch with Sarah and Teddy, meeting with Smithsonian; front yard;; back yard;; living room with Lucy's candle;; study with new curtains, Teddy's painting,; October 15, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 291)
    - City lights and University Stadium from Tumamoc Hill on weekend compared to full moon views at home (garden), October 30, 1971; November 1-4, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 292)
    - Venus and Jupiter, garden at home (fall colors); Sarah in garden;; Venus, Mercury, Moon (Jupiter invisible),; November 13, 1971; November 20, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 293)
    - Sky colors from Tumamoc Hill, snow at home; November 25-December 8, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 294)
    - Venus, Moon, 40” telescope Soldiers Peak; Soldiers Peak horizon;; home oranges,; December 21-23, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 295)
    - Trip to Philadelphia, clouds, trip to NASA, Ames San Francisco; Tumamoc shots, tower;; San Manuel smoke filling San Pedro Valley and Kitt Peak;; Douglas smelter smoke,; December 26-28, 1971,; January 1972 (Box 78, Folder 296)
    - Mt. Lemon ski area, Mt Lemon IR Observatory views; Minnesota dome Kitt Peak from Mt. Lemon smog;; San Pedro Valley smog from vista;; Mt. Hopkins smog from Geology Vista;; Smog in Bear Canyon at sunset;; Kitt Peak at sunset;; crane with Mr. Lance and Mel;; Rancho Sin Vacas;; University farm fire (Campbell Ave),; January 18-31, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 297)
    - Flight to Douglas smelter with Steve Larson, February 13, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 298)
    - Views on Tumamoc of haze toward East and South, Indian defense walls, test telescopes; February 13, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 299)
    - Trip to Albuquerque, Douglas Smelter 120 miles to the north; Morenci smoke, Douglas, Gila River, Duncan, and Silver City;; ripples in smog Silver City to El Paso;; volcano's south of Albuquerque Rio Grande and cloud cap;; contrails over Albuquerque;; broken contrail (wavelike),; February 1972 (Box 78, Folder 300)
    - Kitt Peak series; contrails, clouds, LA to Phoenix, San Gorgonio, CA; Colorado River from about 7000 ft.;; Convair and Lear jet interior shots,; February 27, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 301)
    - Observatory in garden and view from sky, flowers from home; February 27, 1972; March 20, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 302)
    - Douglas smog with SE wind, construction of 21” dome; Malacara visit;; home, Sarah;; assembly of 21” dome,; March 17-28,1972 (Box 78, Folder 303)
    - Spring flowers at home, Paul and Diana home from Egypt; Conjunction of Venus, Mars and Saturn,; April 1972 (Box 78, Folder 304)
    - Flowers at home, Sasha, 21” dome nearly completed at Tumamoc; April 1972 (Box 78, Folder 305)
    - Paul, Diana, Sarah at lunch, flowers at home; the Volkswagen Wagon bus and driver,; May 2, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 306)
    - Trip to Flagstaff, conjunction of Venus, Mars, Saturn; San Manual smog;; Superior plume,; April-May 1972 (Box 78, Folder 307)
    - Lucy's garden, dinner at Livermore; from 70” dome to River Telescope and AFCR;; dome and Fort Huachuca;; picture of Kuiper’s painting;; New York; Columbia University (Amsterdam 116th) river and library,; May 1-21, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 308)
    - Return trip from N.Y. to Tucson via Chicago, pictures, May 23, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 309)
    - Front garden, June 3, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 310)
    - Views of front garden, Dekkes family leaving; June10-11, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 311)